《终空》前情提要
Previously on "Final Space,"
盖瑞在内空见到了波罗
Gary journeys to Inner Space to see the Titan,
一个已经沉睡了一万年的泰坦
Bolo, who's been asleep for 10,000 years.
在内空中  盖瑞的父亲派他去地球
While there, Gary's father tells him to go to Earth
寻找最后一个反物质炸弹
to find the last anti-matter bomb.
借助那个炸弹  他们就能封锁终空
With it, they can close Final Space.
让我们祈祷时间还够用吧
Let's hope there's still time.
嘿！那是小胡子盖瑞吗？
Hey! Is that mustache Gary?
正是在下
It sure is.
盖瑞  还有1分钟  饼干就烤好了
Gary. The cookies will be done in one minute.
好极了  我真的好激动啊...
Oh, good. I'm extremely excited...
有饼干诶
for these cookies.
我好害怕  HUE
I'm scared, H.U.E.
我知道  盖瑞
I know, Gary.
你会一直陪我到最后吗？
You'll stay with me till the end?
我会一直陪你  直到最后的最后
Till the very end.
谢谢你  HUE
Thank you, H.U.E.
我很荣幸  能做你的朋友
It's been an honor to be your friend.
鸭嘴兽字幕组出品
翻译 + 专访听译 + 校对 + 压制：Kyl
Final Space - Chapter Nine
终空  第一季第九集
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
本字幕仅供学习交流  请于下载后24小时内删除
盖瑞  能精确转述一下你爸的指示吗？
Gary, what were your father's exact instructions?
他说  “找到反物质炸弹  然后用它修补缺口”
He said, "Get the anti-matter bomb and close the breach."
他说地球上的那个炸弹在哪了吗？
Did he say where on Earth the bomb is?
在纽约  地球上那个纽约
In New York. The one on Earth.
纽约是个很大的地方
That's a really big place.
盖瑞  我说不定能帮到你
Gary, I might be able to help.
我在你父亲的文件里找到了这个
I have found this in your father's files.
日志2845B...  约翰·古茨比德舰长
Log 2845B ... Captain John Goodspeed.
真是个重大的日子  经过这么长时间  我们终于做到了
Big day. Took forever, but we finally got there.
是反物质炸弹
The anti-matter bomb.
我们在此所做的一切
What we do here could be the difference
关乎地球的幸存
between Earth's survival
抑或是  其于终空中的消亡
and its being swallowed up into Final Space.
约翰  如果咱们做成了
Hey, John, if we survive this,
咱们就去吃顿墨西哥小卷饼庆功  你看怎么样？
what do you say we kick it up with some taquitos, bro?
墨西哥小卷饼（Taquito）：一种墨西哥食品，由油炸玉米薄饼包裹牛肉、鸡肉、或奶酪馅制成。
我要杀了他
I'm going to kill him.
我知道这是哪  就在无疆守卫的塔尖上
I know where that is. It's the Infinity Guard Spire.
所以下一站... 就是那了！
Then next stop ... that place!
哦我的天哪！HUE  发生了什么？
Oh, my gosh! H.U.E., wh... what is going on?
我们在哪？！
Where are we?!
我们在地球  盖瑞
Earth, Gary.
它从坐标上偏离了  正被吸入缺口
It has shifted from its coordinates and is being sucked into the breach.
最先被吸走的就是海水
The oceans are the first to go.
天哪  要来真的了
Oh, my God. It's happening.
都是KVN的错  去死吧  KVN  去死！
I blame KVN. Way to go, KVN. Way to go!
我已经表现得很好了！
I'm getting better!
你越来越烂了  越来越烂！打我那下很疼的！
You're getting worse. So much worse! It hurts!
特别特别疼！
It hurts me physically!
♪ 事情正在变好 ♪
♪ Things are getting better ♪
♪ 层云渐开  阳光普照 ♪
♪ The sun is shining, the clouds are parting ♪
♪ 这个家伙正在进步 ♪
♪ And this guy is making great striiides ♪
一起来！你最棒  KVN
Sing with me! You're doing great, KVN.
谢了！我最棒！
Thanks! I am doing great!
- 哦天哪！   - 这可和想象的不一样
- Oh, my God! - That's different.
- 乌龟？！   - 还是个小乌龟呢
- Turtles?! - That's a little one!
我的个老天爷哪！
Dear Heavenly Lightning Lord!
我们被忍者神龟袭击了！
We're being attacked by Ninja Sea Turtles!
不  盖瑞  是我们游到一群海龟里了
No, Gary. But we have flown into a school of them.
School：双关语，既指“一群水生动物”，又指“学校”。
好的  至少它们还在上学
Good! They're still in school.
Chookity.
这可不对劲  这非常不对劲
This is so wrong. This is very wrong.
纽约
New York.
整个星球都快被遗弃了  盖瑞
The planet has been mostly abandoned, Gary.
看啊  我以前来过纽约
Look at this place. I've been to New York before.
这个纽约...
And this...
这个纽约看上去比之前的好点  不过也没好太多
This looks better. Not by much.
盖瑞  很不幸
Gary, uh-oh.
你只有六个小时去找反物质炸弹
You'll have six hours to locate the anti-matter bomb.
六小时后  你现在看到的都会消失了
After that, all of what you see now will be gone.
无疆守卫背叛了人类
The Infinity Guard betrayed the human race.
他们站好边了  而我们选择另外一边
They chose their side, and we're on the other.
他们将对我们毫不手软  因此我们对他们也要如此
They will show us no mercy, so I suggest we show them none.
现在我们出发  去找炸弹吧
Now let's find that bomb.
我不知道你到底在说些啥  不过...
I have no idea what you're talking about, but...
我  先  溜  了！一会见！
Count. Me. Out! Later!
盖瑞  舰上机器人们
Gary, the S.A.M.E.S.
翻新了等离子体炬和电磁炮
have retrofitted the plasma torches, rail guns,
以及其它的维护设备
and other sundry maintenance equipment
它们现在变成了威猛的超级武器
into heinous super weapons.
好极了  HUE  天哪
Yes, H.U.E.! Good lord, yes!
你知道吗  你已经被我
Do you know what that makes you?
评为“本月之星”了！
That makes you Employee of the freaking Month.
奎恩  我能问你点事吗？
Quinn, can I ask you something?
- 开火！   - 天啦噜  来得也太快了点！
- Fire! - Oh, my ... That came kinda fast!
干掉他们  伙计们！
Take 'em out, boys!
Cookity pok!
冲啊  冲啊  哦！
Go, go, go, go! Oh!
奎恩  我还没问完呢
Quinn, I still have that question.
呀啊！
Yeah!
Woop! Pah!
上啊 月饼！
Go, Mooncake!
好的好的好的！哦  不！
Oh, oh, yes! Yes! Oh, my ... oh, no.
奎恩！还是那个问题
Quinn! About that question.
我想问的是  你愿意
What I wanted to ask is would you like
和我一起喝一杯酒吗？
to drink alcoholic liquids out of a cup with me?
现在？你非得现在问我？
Now? You're asking me this now?
哦  成吧  然后你一个跟头就溜了
Oh, okay, just gonna cartwheel away from me.
哦差点！哦我的天哪！哦！
Okay, that was close! Oh, my God. Ow, ohh! Oh!
但是  我... 奎恩！
But just, you know, I mean... come on, Quinn!
只是... 只是一杯酒而已
It jus... it's just a drink.
我们难道不该专心一点吗？
Shouldn't we be concentrating on this?
我专心不起来  因为我满脑子都是
I can't concentrate on this because all I am thinking about
- 你想不想和我一起出去！   - 那就不想
- is if you wanna go out with me! - Then no.
去死！去死！去死！为什么？
Die! Die! Die! Why?
因为你一个劲地问我想不想去
Because I can't concentrate on killing these guys
我都没法专心杀人了！
if I'm concentrating on that!
有没有人和你说过  应急灯下的你
Did anyone ever tell you emergency lighting
- 无比性感？   - 闭嘴
- brings out your hotness? - Shut up.
啊！
Aah!
哦别担心  盖瑞  KVN能帮忙
Ohhh, don't worry, Gary. KVN can handle this.
KVN  别来帮忙
KVN, don't handle this.
“来帮忙”？我来了！
Handle this? You got it!
KVN  这他喵的都是啥？
KVN, what the freak is that?
你一直有一套机械装甲？！
You just had a mech suit lying around this whole time?!
是呀  所以呢？
Yeah, so?
老天啊  我恨死你了
Good lord, I hate you so feverishly.
好疼  你伤到我了  KVN
It hurts. It physically hurts me, KVN.
- 嘿  看啊  是KVN！   - 你们好啊！
- Hey, look, KVN! - Hey, guys!
- 嘿  KVN   - 你看起来不错
- Hey, KVN. - You look great.
- 嘿  KVN   - ...什么？KVN  是我呀  KVN
- Hey, KVN. - ...What? KVN, it's me ... KVN.
- 我？   - 你！
- Me? - You!
- 嘿  KVN   - 嘿  看啊  是KVN！
- Hey, KVN. - Hey, look, it's KVN.
- 嘿  KVN  你看起来不错！   - 嘿  KVN  你看起来不错！
- Hey, KVN, you look great! - Hi, KVN! You look great!
- 嘿  KVN  快来这里！   - 哪里？
- Hey, KVN, over here! - Where?
- 这里！   - 哈哈！
- Here! - Haha!
别打我们... 去打他们
Don't shoot us ... shoot them.
- 一切为了KVN！   - 一切为了KVN！
- Anything for a KVN! - Anything for a KVN!
- 我帮完忙了！   - 盖瑞  好歹给他个小鼓励
- Handled! - Gary, give him a little something.
- 小鼓励是多小？   - 给他个大拇指？
- How little? - A thumbs up?
呃  好疼啊
Ugh. So much hurt.
我的大拇指... 好疼啊
My thumb ... It's burning.
哦！
Oh!
那我们就  又变回最好的朋友了  你们听见了吗？
We're best friends now. Guys, do you hear this?
- 我俩现在是最好的朋友了   - 咱俩连朋友都算不上
- We're best friends now. - We're not even friends.
对啊  我们不是“朋友”  而是“最好的朋友”
Right. We're best friends.
盖瑞  时间要不够了
Gary, there isn't much time.
我们得在四个小时之内找到炸弹
Only four more hours to locate the bomb
否则地球就会被缺口吸进去了
before the Earth is sucked into the breach.
是炸弹库！我们找到了！
Bomb vault, yo! We found it, guys.
它不见了  去哪了  HUE？我们没时间了
It's gone. Where is it, H.U.E.? We're running out of time.
很可能是那个宇宙白痴叫他的小喽啰们把它藏起来了
Odds are that space douche has instructed his dickheads to hide it.
HUE  你能找到它吗？
H.U.E., can you find it?
呃
Mm-hmm.
啊  所有文件都被删除了
Hmmm. Ah. All files have been deleted.
地点未知
Location unknown.
未知？
Unknown?!
那我们就完蛋了
Then it's over.
放下你们的武器！马上放下！
Drop your weapons! Drop them now!
Chookity!
好吧... 现在才是真的完蛋了
I mean... now it's over.
我之前还以为... 我们那时候就要完蛋了呢
I thought that ... I thought before we were over,
- 不过现在我们才是真的要死了   - 趴在地上！
- but now we are all going to die. - Get down on the floor!
我知道你没问过  不过这就是你依旧单身的原因
Not that you asked, but this is why you're single.
我的确没想问过  不过既然你提到了  给我讲讲呗
I didn't ask. But since you brought it up, enlighten me.
呃  其实我也是才想到的  但...
Okay, well, I actually didn't think that far ahead, but...
盖瑞  你究竟为什么会喜欢我？
Look, Gary, why do you even like me?
因为你能做到我做不到的所有事
Because you're everything I'm not.
- 这是在夸我  是吗？   - 老天啊  当然了
- And that's a good thing, right? - Hell, yeah, it is.
准备行刑
Commencing executions.
把那个小东西带给总司令
Take the life form to the Lord Commander.
等一下  呃  你看  爱不是数学公式
Just a second, guys. Uh, look, love isn't a formula.
它很乱  也很真实  很坦诚
It's messy. It's real. It's raw.
- 受死吧  叛徒   - 那好吧
- Prepare to die, traitor. - Then, yes.
我愿意和你一起喝杯酒
I'll drink liquids with you out of a cup.
一杯酒而已  不成问题
I guess one drink can't hurt.
说再见吧
Say goodbye.
- 抱歉  我来晚了   - 三烦！
- Sorry I'm late. - Tribore!
是三烦吗？正是！
Is it Tribore? It is!
Pachu. Pachu.
Pachu. Pachu. Pachu.
拿上这五个  明天早上再给我打电话吧
Take five and call me in the morning.
来自习语“Take two and call me in the morning”
意为“吃两片药睡一觉，明天早上再给我打电话吧”，用以安慰半夜来诉苦的人.
嘿老兄！我还不知道你是谁  不过我喜欢
Hey, guy! I don't know who you are, but I like how
你明知道他都死了  还要开枪打他的样子
you keep shooting people even after they're dead.
他是不是很棒？他真是太帅了
Isn't he great? He's so handsome.
欢迎加入反抗军
Then welcome to the Resistance.
注意听讲  他在讲话呢
Pay attention. He's talking.
快  跟上我  会有危险吗？
Quick, follow me. Will it be dangerous?
那还用说吗！
You bet'cha!
Chookity!
你在这干什么？！
What are you doing here?!
在总司令把无疆守卫侵蚀以后
When the Lord Commander infiltrated the Infinity Guard,
一支反抗军集结了  他们需要一个领袖
a Resistance rose up and they needed a leader.
他们需要一个至诚的  不可被收买的灵魂
Someone pure of spirit and incorruptible.
只有一个人能满足这个条件
Only one person met those criteria.
- 那就是三烦   - 我还以为你只会
- Tribore. - I thought you've just been
溜进我的房间里穿我的衣服呢
skulking around my apartment wearing my dresses.
我是在表现得深藏不露
I was in deep cover.
我还需要和你解释吗？不  我不需要
Do I have to explain myself to you? I don't.
- 那是我的围巾吗？   - 曾经是
- Is that my scarf? - It was.
你们反抗军会不会碰巧知道
Does this Resistance of yours happen to know
- 反物质炸弹在哪？   - 还不知道
- where an anti-matter bomb is? - Not yet.
理查德？黑进主机里
Richard? Hack into the mainframe.
我们得找到反物质炸弹
We need to find an anti-matter bomb.
- 这边走！   - 太厉害了
- This way! - This is amazing.
所以这就是世界末日了
So this is the end of the world.
我还以为会比这个壮观呢
I was hoping for more.
理查德说这里以前有个秘密基地
Richard said there was a secret base
反物质炸弹就在这里  这真是太理查德了
where the bomb is being kept. That's so Richard.
你想来杯喝的吗？哦对了  你很忙的
Do you want to get a drink? Oh, wait. You're busy.
你怎么会想和我喝酒？
Why would you want to get a drink with me?
只是看着你就足够了...
Just looking at you is enough...
- ...一辈子都看着你   - 这是我们第一次见面的酒吧！
- ...for a lifetime. - This is the bar where we first met!
入口被隐藏住了
The entrance is hidden.
我怎么知道的？我其实不知道
How do I know? I actually don't know.
快过来  KVN  我需要你的感应装置
Come on, KVN. I need your sensors.
我还有感应装置？！KVN万岁！
I have sensors?! Hooray for KVN!
盖瑞  我有感应装置诶！耶！
Gary, I have sensors! Yay!
哦  简直不敢相信... 难以置信
Oh, I can't believe it. Look ... I can't believe it...
所以你要给我买杯酒  还是怎样？
So, are you going to buy me that drink or what?
当然了  我请你喝  挑一杯吧
Hell, yeah, I am. Pick your poison.
所以我猜  这就是咱们的第一次约会吧
So, I guess, I'm just saying, this is our first date.
啊我要死了！我们已经进入无意义的虚空了！
I'm gonna die! We're entering the meaningless void!
- 干杯   - 人类文明至此而止！
- Cheers. - Civilization ends now!
咔哒
Glass clink.
是三烦找到的吗？正是！
Did Tribore find it? He did!
并不是因为有理查德  他老是那么理查德
No thanks to Richard, which, again, is so Richard.
啊！
Aah!
不可能的吧
No freaking way.
五年前我一记空手切  扒下了这个人的衣服
Five years ago I karate chopped this man to steal his clothes.
呀！
Schwa!
走你！
Swallow!
你是个好人  盖瑞！
You're a good guy, Gary!
没人帮他的吗？！
Did not anyone help him?!
- 你个烂人   - 他还活着
- Oh, you jerk face. - He's still alive.
我给他吃了阿司匹林...
I gave him aspirin ...
哦不  我给成“太懦”了  哦  还给过量了
No, I gave him Crylenol. Oh, and I overdosed him.
你不是个好人  盖瑞
You're not a good guy, Gary.
你是个如此可怕的人类！
Oh, you're such a terrible human being!
KVN  你找到什么值得汇报的东西了吗？
KVN, are you detecting anything worth chatting about?
没呢  没呢
Nope. Nope.
哦  其实我找到了！
Ooh, I mean yes!
秘密地下厕所已开启
Secret underground bathroom base now accessible.
赞！
Tight!
盖瑞  表层下方17米处有个加固的混凝土结构
Gary, there is a reinforced concrete structure 17 meters below the surface.
并不想扫兴  不过缺口对地球的影响
Not to be a buzzkill, but the breach's effect on the Earth
即将达到临界质量
is reaching critical mass.
临界质量（critical mass）：维持核子连锁反应所需的裂变材料质量。
超过此质量会引发产生连锁反应。
盖瑞  你能别做那张脸了吗  抓紧时间
Gary, would you stop making the face and hurry up?
盖瑞  我监测到大剂量的反物质
Gary, I am detecting very high levels of anti-matter.
三烦  干得不错
Tribore. You did an okay job.
这诚然是很好的成果  的确很好！
It was nice work. It was!
炸弹就在这里面  你们大家退后
The bomb's in there. You guys, stay back.
我进去把他拿来
I'm goin' in to get it.
啊啊啊！
Ah, uh, aah!
- 快跑！   - 小心  盖瑞！
- Run! - Careful, Gary!
结构即将坍塌
Structural collapse imminent.
快出去！如果我九点钟之前把你送回家了
Get out! If I get you home by nine,
我有多大可能和你进行嘴对嘴运动？
what are my chances of getting some lip-to-lip action?
- 我认为有中等可能   - 中等？
- I'm gonna go with moderate. - Moderate?
我的老天哪  我的裤子都绷紧了
Oh good lord, my slacks are tightening.
现在先专心点  牛仔
Settle down, Cowboy.
- 哇哇哇哇哇   - 啊
- Wah-wah-wah-wah-wah. - Aah.
- 盖瑞...   - 什么事？
- Gary ... - What's up?
第一次约会挺不错的
This is actually a pretty good first date.
- 啊！   - 奎恩！
- Ugh! - Quinn!
奎恩！！
Quinn!!
小卡多！把这个送回船上  蜘蛛猫
Little Cato! Get this back to the ship, Spider Cat.
没问题  闪电侠盗
You got it, Thunder Bandit.
盖瑞  你的速度不足以赶上奎恩
Gary, you do not have the required speed to reach Quinn
在此之前  她会被水压杀死的
before the pressure kills her.
谁说我只有一个人的？
Who said it was just going to be me?
月饼  双倍加速！
Mooncake, double time it!
Chokity!
Chok chok chok chok chok chok chok chok!
HUE！深度是多少
H.U.E.! Distance.
130英尺  即将到达粉碎深度
130 feet. Approaching crush depth.
粉碎深度（crush depth）：计算得出的深度，在此之下潜水设备会被水压挤碎。
我能看见她的灯
I can see her light.
我不建议你继续下潜了
I would advise you to go no further.
正如所想的一样  你肯定不听我的... 所以请加快速度
Seeing as I know you won't listen to me...  hurry.
HUE  这是什么？
H.U.E., what is this?
我监测到大量岩浆
I am detecting high levels of magma
它们即将冲破地壳
about to break through the Earth's crust.
哦  不...
Oh, no...
月饼！三倍加速！哦不！
Mooncake! Triple time! Oh, no!
啊！啊！
Aah! Aah!
启动重力靴！
Activate gravity boots!
HUE  你要去哪？
H.U.E.! Where are you going?
别担心  我们不会抛下盖瑞的
Don't worry, we will not leave Gary.
冲啊  冲啊  冲啊  月饼！冲啊！
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, Mooncake! Go!!
哦  冲冲冲  冲啊  冲啊！
Ohhh, go, go, go, go, go!
Wa-ehhhhh...
Chokity!!
不至于那么激动吧
It's not that impressive.
月饼  原来你在那啊
Mooncake, there you are.
♪ If only I could fix the sky... ♪
♪ 如果我能弥合天空... ♪
不  不  不不不... HUE！
No, no, no, no, no. No... H.U.E.!
♪ It's got a way of knowing when to hurt me ♪
♪ 有种方法知道  何时会伤到我 ♪
♪ Oh, it's when the night is long ♪
♪ 哦  当漫漫长夜降临 ♪
我在哪？我记得... 我在厕所里啊
Where am I? I remember... I was in the bathroom.
我拉上了裤链  然后...
I had zippered my pants, and then...
哦我的老天哪！啊！
Oh, my God! Aah!
天哪！好极了...
Oh God! Okay...
你个白痴！你个大白痴！
You jerk! You jerk face!
♪ Earthquakes break and shatter the perfect design ♪
♪ 大地震颤  精巧的造物粉碎 ♪
- 盖瑞？   - 你醒了
- Gary? - You're back.
还以为我失去你了呢
Thought I lost you.
- 我们在哪？   - 现在吗...
- Where are we? - Currently...
现在  呃  我们正被拉上太空
well, uh, we're being yanked into space.
♪ Towers rise to meet and hear its laughter ♪
♪ 危塔直抵高空  倾听它的笑声 ♪
也许是我在胡思乱想...
Maybe it's because my head is in the clouds ...
Head in the clouds：双关语，既指“胡思乱想”，
又描述了他们被吸走时“身在云中”的场景。
这可逗不笑你  哈
Not gonna laugh at that one, okay. Ha.
我还以为你会笑呢...
I was hoping for a laugh there ...
有没有可能  你会想每天都
Would you perchance want to join forces with me
和我在一起？
on a daily basis?
我会说“有可能”吧
I'm gonna give that a hard "maybe."
我信你的了！听见了吗  地球！
I'll take it! Are you hearing this, Earth?
我们“有可能”在一起！耶！！
We're hard maybes! Yes!!
HUE  设一条去缺口的航线
H.U.E.! Set a course for the breach.
明明可以简简单单地结束
This could have been so easy.
不过一次又一次  你总选那条更难走的路
But time and time again, you chose the harder path.
那条更黑暗的路
The darker path.
时候到了  你会知道你的选择的后果的
It's time for you to see that your choices have consequences.
我会给你最后一个机会  把月饼交出来
I will give you one last chance to hand over Mooncake.
Chookity.
- 绝不   - 他是我们的一员
- Hell. No. - He is one of us.
我和他不太熟  不过他看起来很受欢迎
I don't really know him. But he seems very popular.
- 他要和我们在一起   - 永不分离
- He stays with us. - Never.
那就准备受死吧！
Then death it is!
我来了
I'm coming for you.
啊  对了  我以前见过这张脸
Ah, yes, I've seen that face before.
一张败北的脸
The face of loss.
反物质炸弹在我们手里！
We have the anti-matter bomb!
我们会把缺口合上... 而你会死掉！
We will close the breach ... you will die!
我很期待
I look forward to it.
我监测到一支由重型火炉舰组成的超级舰队正在靠近
I'm detecting the approach of an armada of heavy incinerators.
- 所有人都会死的   - 不错
- Everyone's gonna die. - You aren‘t wrong.
“他们”都会死的
They're all going to die.
他想挑起战争  那我们就满足他  我们将与他对峙
If he wants a war, he's got one. Let's do this.
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
幕后专访
INSIDE THE EPISODE
三烦是奎恩的同事  然而观众们实在太喜欢他了
Tribore was a co-worker for Quinn, and then people liked him so much that
他最终重返银幕  成为了反抗军领袖
he comes back as the leader of the Resistance.
很搞笑的一点是...
And it's so ridiculous...
我没有任何针对海龟的意思
I don't have anything against sea turtles.
它们很棒  但是濒临灭绝...  我记得濒临灭绝了
Sea turtles are great. They are endangered... I think they're endangered.
奎恩最终和盖瑞第一次一起喝了酒  就在第一集的那个酒吧
When Quinn finally has her first drink with Gary in the same bar as Episode 1,
我们想让它成为他们的初次约会
we really wanted to make this first date,
纵使外面的世界已经岌岌可危
while the world is seemed to being destroyed.
何不如此？世界末日就要来了  让我们喝一杯吧！
Why not? World's ending. Let's have that drink!